Inventory of the Colby E. "Babe" Slater Collection D-394
University of California, Davis General Library, Dept. of Special Collections
- Photographic Materials, 1906-1961; Series 5; 153 prints and 45 negatives.
  - Photographic Prints, 1906-1961; Subseries 5.1; 153 prints.
    - Family and Friends, 1906-1961; D394.5.1.6; 27 photographic prints (Box 2, Folder 17-36)
      - Lodge at Twain Harte, California?, undated; D394.5.1.6.27; 1 photographic print black and white 6 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 30)
        "Babe" Slater vacationed here sometimes with the Lawlor and the Lockhart families.
      - People playing in the snow, undated; D394.5.1.6.28; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 11 cm (Box 3, Folder 31.1)
        Three men and one women posing in the snow. "Snow picture" written on print.
      - People playing in the snow, undated; D394.5.1.6.29; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 11 cm (Box 3, Folder 31.2)
        Three men and one woman posing in snow. Three of the figure are posed holding "snowballs."
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater playing golf, undated; D394.5.1.6.30; 1 photographic print black and white 12 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 32.1)
      - Unidentified man playing golf [Bob Lockhart?], undated; D394.5.1.6.31; 1 photographic print black and white 12 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 32.2)
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater by Government Liquor Control Board, British Columbia, undated; D394.5.1.6.32; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater with Clarksburg friends in front of Gus Olson's home, undated; D394.5.1.6.33; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 10 cm (Box 3, Folder 34.1)
        Front Row feft to right: Bob Yelland, John Wilkins, Norman Lawlor, Ed Davis. Middle row left to right: Gus Olson, Howard Reamer, George Wilson. Back Row left to right: "Babe" Slater (holding baby), unidentified, Bud Schwartz.
        Clarksburg (Calif.) -- History; Slater, Colby E.
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater with Clarksburg friends in front of Gus Olson's home, undated; D394.5.1.6.34; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 10 cm (Box 3, Folder 34.2)
        Left to right: "Babe" Slater, Gus Olson, Howard Reamer?, Ed Davis, Bud Schwartz, Bob Yelland, John Wilkins, George Wilson, unidentified, Norman Lawlor.
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater with Ermal Lawlor, Betty Olson, and friends, undated; d394.5.1.6.35; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Colby E. "Babe" Slater with Jesse Cave and Jesse's wife Virginia Barbour Cave?, undated; D394.5.1.6.36; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 6 cm (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Family Albums and Scrapbooks (reproductions), D394.5.1.6.37 (Box 12)
        Ten wire-bound color reproductions of family photograph albums.
    - Unidentified, 1924, undated; D394.5.1.7; 33 prints. (Box 3, Folder 37-51)
      - Bridge with people and automobile, undated; D394.5.1.7.1; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Shipyard, Europe?, undated; D394.5.1.7.2; 1 photographic print black and white 5 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 38.1)
        Shipyards
      - Buildings, Europe?, undated; D394.5.1.7.3; 1 photographic print black and white 5 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 38.2)
      - Unidentified building on river, Europe?, undated; D394.5.1.7.4; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 39.1)
      - Unidentified factory? on river, Europe?, undated; D394.5.1.7.5; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 39.2)
      - Lefèvre-Utile bakery, Nantes, France?, undated; D394.5.1.7.6; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 15 cm (Box 3, Folder 40.1)
      - Unidentified tower and homes, France?, undated; D394.5.1.7.7; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 15 cm (Box 3, Folder 40.2)
      - Equestrian statue of King Louis XIV, Versailles, France, undated; D394.5.1.7.8; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Unidentified buildings with scaffolding, Europe?, undated; D394.5.1.7.9; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 42.1)
      - Unidentified building with scaffolding and dwellings on a square, Europe?, undated; D394.5.1.7.10; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 42.2)
      - Cologne Cathedral, undated; D394.5.1.7.11; 1 photographic print black and white 12 x 8 cm (Box 3, Folder 43.1)
        Kölner Dom
      - Cologne Cathedral, undated; D394.5.1.7.12; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 6 cm (Box 3, Folder 43.2)
      - Cattle resting on side of a road in front of a split rail fence, undated; D394.5.1.7.13; 1 photographic print black and white (Box 3, Folder 44.3)
        Cattle
      - Man standing in barn doorway, undated; D394.5.1.7.14; 1 photographic print black and white 8 x 6 cm (Box 3, Folder 44.4)
      - Man posing with steer?, undated; D394.5.1.7.15; 1 photographic print black and white 6 x 8 cm (Box 3, Folder 44.5)
      - Cow standing in pasture, undated; D394.5.1.7.16; 1 photographic print black and white 5 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 44.6)
      - Man posing with bull, undated; D394.5.1.7.17; 1 photographic print black and white 8 x 6 cm (Box 3, Folder 44.7)
      - Man posing with steer?, undated; D394.5.1.7.18; 1 photographic print black and white 5 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 44.8)
      - Man posing with heifer?, undated; D394.5.1.7.19; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 5 cm (Box 3, Folder 44.9)
      - Two men posing with a bull, undated; D394.5.1.7.20; 1 photographic print black and white 6 x 8 cm (Box 3, Folder 44.10)
      - Farm buildings, undated; D394.5.1.7.21; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 15 cm (Box 3, Folder 45)
        Agriculture -- California
      - Latona Fountain, Versailles, France, 1924; D394.5.1.7.22; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 10 cm (Box 3, Folder 46)
        Château de Versailles (Versailles, France)
      - Horse posed in front of a barn, undated; D394.5.1.7.23; 1 photographic print black and white 5 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 47)
        Horses
      - Unidentified image of dirt road in front of a field with mountain in background, undated; D394.5.1.7.24; 1 photographic print black and white 5 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 48.1)
      - Unidentified image of shoreline?, undated; D394.5.1.7.25; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 6 cm (Box 3, Folder 48.2)
      - Bird's-eye image of unidentified town, undated; D394.5.1.7.26; 1 photographic print black and white 5 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 48.3)
      - Unidentified glacier?, undated; D394.5.1.7.27; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 5 cm (Box 3, Folder 48.4)
        Glaciers
      - Unidentified glacier?, undated; D394.5.1.7.28; 1 photographic print black and white 9 x 6 cm (Box 3, Folder 48.5)
      - Rugby match, undated; D394.5.1.7.29; 1 photographic print black and white 10 x 12 cm (Box 3, Folder 49.1)
        Rugby football
      - Rugby match, undated; D394.5.1.7.30; 1 photographic print black and white 10 x 12 cm (Box 3, Folder 49.2)
      - Football game, undated; D394.5.1.7.31; 1 photographic print black and white 5 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 50)
        Football
      - Unidentified sailing ship, undated; D394.5.1.7.32; 1 photographic print black and white 10 x 6 cm (Box 3, Folder 51.1)
        Sailing ships
      - Unidentified ocean liner, undated; D394.5.1.7.33; 1 photographic print black and white 7 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 51.2)
        Ocean liners
  - Negatives, 1924, undated; Subseries 5.2; 45 images
    Some negatives correspond to prints in this collection. Most of the negatives are unidentified. They appear to have been made in the early twentieth century and include images of people, automobiles, buildings, livestock, and other subjects.
    - Colby E. "Babe" Slater, his mother Lousie, and his brother Norman, circa 1924; D394.5.2.1; 1 negative black and white 5 x 8 cm (Box 3, Folder 52)
      Slater, Colby E.; Slater, Norman B., Jr., 1919-2013
    - Bridge with people and automobile, undated; D394.5.2.2; 1 negative black and white 7 x 8 cm (Box 3, Folder 53.1)
    - Bridge with people and automobile, undated; D394.5.2.3; 1 photographic print black and white 6 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 53.2)
    - Equestrian statue of Louis XIV, Versailles France and unidentified factory? on river, Europe?, undated; D394.5.2.4; 1 negative black and white 19 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Unidentified buildings with scaffolding and unidentified building with scaffolding and dwellings on a square, Europe?, undated; D394.5.2.5; 1 negative black and white 19 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Cattle herd, undated; D394.5.2.6; 1 negative black and white 5 x 8 cm (Box 3, Folder 56.1)
    - Man posing with steer?, undated; D394.5.2.7; 1 negative black and white 5 x 8 cm (Box 3, Folder 56.2)
    - Man posing with heifer?, undated; D394.5.2.8; 1 negative black and white 5 x 8 cm (Box 3, Folder 56.3)
    - Man standing in barn doorway, undated; D394.5.2.9; 1 negative black and white 7 x 5 cm (Box 3, Folder 56.4)
    - Man posing with bull, undated; D394.5.2.10; 1 negative black and white 8 x 5 cm (Box 3, Folder 56.5)
    - Cow standing in pasture, undated; D394.5.2.11; 1 negative black and white 5 x 8 cm (Box 3, Folder 56.6)
    - Man posing with two cows, undated; D394.5.2.12; 1 negative black and white 5 x 8 cm (Box 3, Folder 56.7)
    - Farm buildings, undated; D394.5.2.13; 1 negative black and white 5 x 8 cm (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Latona Fountain, Versailles and Rugby match, Paris, France, undated; D394.5.2.14; 1 negative black and white 7 x 19 cm (Box 3, Folder 58)
      Château de Versailles (Versailles, France); Rugby football
    - Two men standing on the east steps of the United States Capitol, undated; D394.5.2.15; 1 negative black and white 9 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 59.1)
      United States Capitol (Washington, D.C.)
    - Two men standing on the east steps of the United States Capitol, undated; D394.5.2.16; 1 negative black and white 10 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 59.2)
    - Two men posing in front of the west side of United States Capitol, undated; D394.5.2.17; 1 negative black and white 6 x 12 cm (Box 3, Folder 59.3)
    - Person wearing glasses, undated; D394.5.2.18; 1 negative black and white 7 x 5 cm (Box 3, Folder 60.1)
      Darker of two negatives.
    - Person wearing glasses, undated; D394.5.2.19; 1 negative black and white 8 x 5 cm (Box 3, Folder 60.2)
      Lighter of two negatives.
    - Man with two women, undated; D394.5.2.20; 1 negative black and white 8 x 5 cm (Box 3, Folder 60.3)
      Of two negatives this one is not as sharply focused.
    - Man and two women, undated; D394.5.2.21; 1 negative black and white 8 x 5 cm (Box 3, Folder 60.4)
      Sharper focused of two negatives.
    - Women on front porch, undated; D394.5.2.22; 1 negative black and white 5 x 8 cm (Box 3, Folder 60.5)
    - Person on front porch of house, undated; D394.5.2.23; 1 negative black and white 5 x 7 cm (Box 3, Folder 60.6)
    - Group of people standing by California Farm Bureau, undated; D594.5.2.24; 1 negative black and white 7 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 61.1)
      Agriculture -- California; California Farm Bureau Federation
    - Group of people by railroad cars, undated; D594.5.2.25; 1 negative black and white 7 x 9 cm (Box 3, Folder 61.2)
    - Large group of people gathered in front of building, undated; D394.5.2.26; 1 negative black and white 7 x 10 cm (Box 3, Folder 61.3)
    - Man exercising, undated; D394.5.2.27; 1 negative black and white 8 x 5 (Box 3, Folder 61.4)
    - Soldiers on deck of ship, 1918; D394.5.2.7.28; 1 negative black and white 7 x 10 cm (Box 3, Folder 61.5)
    - Big tent, undated; D394.5.2.29; 1 negative black and white 5 x 8 cm (Box 3, Folder 61.6)
    - Three women standing next to an automobile, undated; D394.5.2.30; 1 negative black and white 5 x 8 cm (Box 4, Folder 1.1)
      Automobiles
    - Little boy and girl, undated; D394.5.2.31; 1 negatives black and white 5 x 8 cm (Box 4, Folder 1.2)
    - Person holding photo, undated; D394.5.2.32; 1 negative black and white 5 x 8 cm (Box 4, Folder 1.3)
    - Baby, undated; D394.5.2.33; 1 negative black and white 8 x 5 cm (Box 4, Folder 1.4)
    - Man and baby, undated; D394.5.2.34; 1 negative black and white 8 x 5 cm (Box 4, Folder 1.5)
    - Grinning man, undated; D394.5.2.35; 1 negative black and white 8 x 5 cm (Box 4, Folder 1.6)
    - Women standing near tree, undated; D394.5.2.36; 1 negative black and white 8 x 5 cm (Box 4, Folder 2.1)
    - Woman holding a pig, undated; D394.5.2.37; 1 negative black and white 8 x 5 cm (Box 4, Folder 2.2)
    - Woman sitting on stairs, undated; D394.5.2.38 (Box 4, Folder 2.3)
    - Two women on stairs, undated; D394.5.2.39; 1 negative black and white 8 x 5 cm (Box 4, Folder 2.4)
    - Woman in coat, undated; D394.5.2.40; 1 negative black and white 7 x 5 cm (Box 4, Folder 2.5)
    - Woman reclining outdoors, undated; D394.5.2.41; 1 negative black and white 5 x 8 cm (Box 4, Folder 2.6)
    - Woman walking, undated; D394.5.2.42; 1 negative black and white 8 x 5 cm (Box 4, Folder 2.7)
- Scrapbook, 1924; Series 6; 46 folders.
  This scrapbook was compiled by Babe Slater's mother, Louise. It contains newspaper clippings, photographs, and ephemera related to Slater winning an Olympic gold medal as captain of the United States Olympic Rugby Team during the 1924 Paris Olympic Games. When the collection was processed, items were removed from the scrapbook and placed in acid-free folders. The scrapbook pages were scanned before they were disassembled in order to keep a record of the original positions of items on the pages. Preservation photocopies of newspaper clippings were also made.
  - Reproductions of scrapbook pages and newspaper clippings, D394.6.1; 2 folders (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1924; D394.6.2; 12 folders (Box 4, Folder 5-15)
    - Clipping, Woodland Daily Democrat. Slater friendship fund big success, March 13, 1924; D394.6.2.1 (Box 4, Folder 5.1)
    - Clipping, Yolo well represented, [1924]; D394.6.2.2 (Box 4, Folder 5.2)
      Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E.; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, [Woodland Daily Democrat]. Community catches spirit of testimonial for Babe Slater, [1924]; D394.6.2.3 (Box 4, Folder 5.3)
    - Clipping, [Woodland Daily Democrat]. 130 "kids" give coppers for their idol, [1924]; D394.6.2.4 (Box 4, Folder 5.4)
    - Clipping, An appreciation of Slater, by Leander Turney, [1924]; D394.6.2.5 (Box 4, Folder 5.5)
    - Clipping, Woodland Daily Democrat. Overcome by friendship testimonial, Babe Slater gets, watch, chain, charms, March 14, 1924; D394.6.2.6 (Box 4, Folder 5.6)
    - Clipping, Chronicle sport editor praises movement in behalf of Babe Slater, [1924]; D394.6.2.7 (Box 4, Folder 5.7)
    - Clipping, [Woodland Daily Democrat]. Sacramentoans pay respects to sportsman, March 8, 1924; D394.6.2.8 (Box 4, Folder 5.8)
    - Clipping, Sacramento Union. Put and take, by Win J. Cutter, March 8, 1924; D394.6.2.9 (Box 4, Folder 5.9)
    - Clipping, [San Francisco Chronicle?]. Giving Babe Slater the credit due, [1924]; D394.6.2.10 (Box 4, Folder 5.10)
      "This is Monday's Chronicle."
    - Clipping, Woodland raises a purse for star footballer, [1924]; D394.6.2.11 (Box 4, Folder 5.11)
    - Clipping, [Woodland Daily Democrat]. These kids pull hard for Slater, March 8, 1924; D394.6.2.12 (Box 4, Folder 5.12)
      Esparto (Calif.) -- History; Slater, Colby E.
    - Clipping, Fans make register jingle for Slater, [1924]; D394.6.2.13 (Box 4, Folder 5.13)
    - Clipping, "Babe's" brother selected to make trip to Olympiad, [1924]; D394.6.2.14 (Box 4, Folder 5.14)
      Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E.; Slater, Norman B. (Norman Bernard), 1894-1979; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, Monday your last day to subscribe to Slater Fund, March 8, 1924; D394.6.2.15 (Box 4, Folder 5.15)
    - Clipping, Slater first on list chosen for Olympiad, [1924]; D394.6.2.16 (Box 4, Folder 5.16)
      Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E.; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France); Olympic Games (7th: 1920: Antwerp, Belgium)
    - Clipping, Slater star of game, cinches Paris trip, [1924]; D394.6.2.17 (Box 4, Folder 5.17)
    - Clipping, Woodland Daily Democrat. Sacramento sports editor catches Slater germ; lauds him as "real sportsman, real man" to aid fund, March 8, 1924; D394.6.2.18 (Box 4, Folder 5.18)
    - Clipping, St. Thomas Times-Journal, Canada. U.S. Olympic rugbyists enjoy brief stop here, April 6, 1924; D394.6.2.19 (Box 4, Folder 6.1)
    - Clipping, [St. Thomas Times-Journal, Canada.] U.S. Olympic rugbyists send greeting to city, [April 1924]; D394.6.2.20 (Box 4, Folder 6.2)
    - Clipping, Captain Slater writes, [1924]; D394.6.2.21 (Box 4, Folder 6.3)
      Headline only.
    - Clipping, San Francisco Examiner. U.S. Rugby team on way to Olympic Games, by Harry M. Hayward, [1924]; D394.6.2.22 (Box 4, Folder 6.4)
      Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E.; Slater, Norman B. (Norman Bernard), 1894-1979; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, Slater, Farrish off to Olympiad, [1924]; D394.6.2.23; 3 clippings (Box 4, Folder 6.5)
    - Clipping, Rugby football: Blackheath v. the Americans, [1924]; D394.6.2.24; 2 clippings (Box 4, Folder 7.1)
      Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States
    - Clipping, The Evening Times, London. U.S. rugby XV's first real "try-out": Olympic Games aspirants of little experience, [1924]; D394.6.2.25 (Box 4, Folder 7.2)
    - Clipping, U.S. rugby team impresses French, [1924]; D394.6.2.26 (Box 4, Folder 7.3)
      Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E.; Olympic Games (7th: 1920: Antwerp, Belgium); Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, Olympic rugby team at Plymouth, [1924]; D394.6.2.27 (Box 4, Folder 7.4)
      Photographs of team. Caption: "Within a short time of their arrival at Plymouth yesterday, [the] Olympic Rugby team from America went to the Rectory Football Ground in order to practice. Our photographer, after taking this group, photographed the [men] playing, and also procured a characteristic 'snap' of Patrick, the full-back, putting the ball to touch."
      Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E.; Slater, Norman B. (Norman Bernard), 1894-1979
    - Clipping, British premier ruggers win from Slater's Yanks; practice event 13 to 9, [1924]; D394.6.2.28 (Box 4, Folder 7.5)
      Rugby football teams -- United States; Rugby football; Slater, Colby E.
    - Clipping, American loss: Harlequins win last game of tour, by Dark Blue, [1924]; D394.6.2.29 (Box 4, Folder 7.6)
    - Clipping, Daily Mirror. Fright for Blackheath: America's fine Olympic rugby team only just fail at Teddington, [1924]; D394.6.2.30 (Box 4, Folder 7.7)
    - Clipping, The Evening News. Curious American ruggers, [1924]; D394.6.2.31 (Box 4, Folder 7.8)
      Rugby football; Rugby football teams -- United States; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, Americans win: Captain Babe Slaters team beats Britishers, [1924]; D394.6.2.32 (Box 4, Folder 8.1)
    - Clipping, Sam Goodman wins fight for rugby picture rights, May 9, [1924]; D394.6.2.33 (Box 4, Folder 8.2)
    - Clipping, Will head American ruggers against Rumania, [1924]; D394.6.2.34 (Box 4, Folder 8.3)
      Photograph of Babe Slater. Caption: "Colby Slater, captain of the American Olympic Games rugby team scheduled to play Rumania tomorrow in the first championship match."
      Rugby football; Slater, Colby E.; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, Rugby football: The American players at Twickenham, [1924]; D394.6.2.35; 2 clippings (Box 4, Folder 8.4)
    - Clipping, Britons again defeat Slater's American eleven, [1924]; D394.6.2.36 (Box 4, Folder 8.5)
    - Clipping, Les deux capitaines des équipes du match de rugby France-Angleterre, [1924]; D394.6.2.37 (Box 4, Folder 8.6)
      Caricatures of team captains.
      Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France); Slater, Colby E.
    - Clipping, Yesterday's rugby: American XV. beaten by 'Quins, by D.R. Gent, [1924]; D394.6.2.38 (Box 4, Folder 8.7)
    - Clipping, American rugby players. Impressions at Devonport, [1924]; D394.6.2.39 (Box 4, Folder 8.8)
    - Clipping, C. Slater, Capitaine de l'équipe américaine de rugby, [1924]; D394.6.2.40 (Box 4, Folder 8.9)
      Photograph of Babe Slater.
    - Clipping, [N]ews and Mercury. Plenty of pluck, April 22, [1924]; D394.6.2.41 (Box 4, Folder 8.10)
      Photograph of match. Caption: "Although Devonport Services suffered defeat in their match with the American Olympic Rugby team at the Rectory yesterday they played a plucky game. A "Services" midget tackles an American giant."
    - Clipping, Mid-week pictorial. American Olympic rugby team which sailed recently for France to participate in the international athletic struggle at Paris. Several of them were members of the Olympic team of 1920, April 17, 1924; D394.6.2.42 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Team portrait.
      Rugby football teams -- United States; Slater, Colby E.; Slater, Norman B. (Norman Bernard), 1894-1979; Olympic Games (7th: 1920: Antwerp, Belgium); Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, Les États-Unis gagnent la première victoire olympique, [1924]; D394.6.2.43 (Box 4, Folder 10.1)
      Drawings of three players.
      Rugby football; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France)
    - Clipping, American rugby team will play Rumania today, [1924]; D394.6.2.44 (Box 4, Folder 10.2)
    - Clipping, [Woodland Daily Democrat?]. Yanks' triumph causes joy here, [1924]; D394.6.2.45 (Box 4, Folder 10.3)
      Rugby football; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France); Slater, Colby E.; Slater, Norman B. (Norman Bernard), 1894-1979
    - Clipping, Le tournoi olympique de rugby: États-Unis contre Roumanie aujourd'hui à Colombes, [1924]; D394.6.2.46 (Box 4, Folder 10.4)
      Rugby football; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France); Slater, Norman B. (Norman Bernard), 1894-1979
    - Clipping, La mascotte des rugbymen américains, [1924]; D394.6.2.47 (Box 4, Folder 10.5)
      Photograph. Caption: "Mme. Luella Melais remet au capitaine de l'équipe américaine olympique de rugby, une mascotte: Cali."
      Rugby football teams -- United States; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France); Slater, Colby E.
    - Clipping, American rugby team, [1924]; D394.6.2.48 (Box 4, Folder 10.6)
      Team photograph.
    - Clipping, États-Unis contre France, [1924]; D394.6.2.49 (Box 4, Folder 11.1)
      Rugby football; Olympic Games (8th: 1924: Paris, France); Slater, Colby E.
    - Clipping, Les États-Unis battent la Roumanie, [1924]; D394.6.2.50 (Box 4, Folder 11.2)
    - Clipping, Pour France-Amérique, [1924]; D394.6.2.51 (Box 4, Folder 11.3)
    - Clipping, Roumanie-Amérique, [1924]; D394.6.2.52 (Box 4, Folder 11.4)
    - Clipping, Une visite au quartier général yankee, [1924]; D394.6.2.53; 2 clippings (Box 4, Folder 11.5)
    - Clipping, Les joueurs Américains, [1924]; D394.6.2.54 (Box 4, Folder 11.6)
      Photographs and drawings of players.
    - Clipping, Avec le tournoi de Rugby le rideau se lève sur les Jeux Olympiques: Le match France-Roumanie, [1924]; D394.6.2.55 (Box 4, Folder 11.7)
    - Clipping, C'est le pavillon étoilé qui a inauguré le mât olympique, [1924]; D394.6.2.56 (Box 4, Folder 11.8)
    - Clipping, Notes sur les joueurs. États-Unis, [1924]; D394.6.2.57 (Box 4, Folder 11.9)
    - Clipping, Le tournoi olympique: le match États-Unis-France, [1924]; D394.6.2.58 (Box 4, Folder 11.10)
      Photograph. Caption: "Béhotéguy, mis en posession de la balle, part à l'attaque s'apprêtant à passer à Jarréguy. C'est au cours de cette phase de jeu que notre sympathique ailier international manqua de fort peu la réussite d'un essai."